{
    "subject": "resource/Antz",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Eric_Darnell",
    "human_readable": "Eric Darnell directed Antz.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9114750027656555,
            "question": "Name a movie directed by Eric Darnell."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819394707679749,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Eric Darnell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8606432676315308,
            "question": "Eric Darnell is known for directing which animated film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8198440074920654,
            "question": "Eric Darnell's notable work includes directing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7443225979804993,
            "question": "What film did Eric Darnell direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7407125234603882,
            "question": "What movie did Eric Darnell helm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7365128397941589,
            "question": "Which movie is associated with Eric Darnell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047408819198608,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Antz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5578681230545044,
            "question": "Who was the director behind Antz?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46777239441871643,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Antz?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Darnell directed Antz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7711_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the director behind Antz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7711_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the movie Antz?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7711_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which movie is associated with Eric Darnell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7711_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7711_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about Eric Darnell's career and filmography, including his role as co-director of the animated hits \"Antz\" (1998) and \"Madagascar\" (2005). Therefore, the triple \"Eric Darnell directed Antz.\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Eric Darnell co-directed the animated film \"Antz\" with Tim Johnson, which supports the statement that Eric Darnell directed Antz."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}